<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com</id>
    <title>Best Choice</title>
    <updated>2023-11-10T05:19:44.271Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>We choose the best products in the market for you.</subtitle>
    <logo>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2023, Best Choice</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best wireless chargers for iPhone and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-wireless-chargers-for-iphone-and-android/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-wireless-chargers-for-iphone-and-android/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-09T05:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Step into the cableless future with the best wireless chargers on this guide. You don't need to go hunting for the end of your USB-C or Lightning charger when you need to power up your phone, but instead leave your phone on a stand or pad and let the magic of magnetic induction do the work.</p>
<p>Take a look at our best wireless chargers below.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699507244266.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1belkin-boost-charge-pro-3-in-1-wireless-charging-pad-with-magsafe">1.Belkin Boost Charge Pro 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Pad with MagSafe</h1>
<p><strong>Ther best wireless charger overall</strong></p>
<p>This three-in-one charging pad from Belkin is my current favorite wireless charger. It offers 15W MagSafe charging for the iPhone 12 and iPhone 13, as well as fast charging for the Apple Watch 7 and regular wireless charging in an AirPods-sized recess, meaning all my Apple mobile devices could charge simultaneously from a single charging brick. That brick comes included too, so I didn't have to go rooting around in a cupboard for one with the correct wattage.</p>
<p>The only thing holding this charger back from perfection is its price, which is quite high. Also, the use of MagSafe and the Apple Watch charging cradle means this isn't a great pick for Android users.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B09XQPLBSB&asins=B09XQPLBSB&linkId=038cd021173aa7098372f595bddace5a&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699507345190.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2apple-magsafe-charger">2.Apple MagSafe Charger</h1>
<p><strong>The best wireless charger to get for your iPhone</strong></p>
<p>As an iPhone 14 owner, Apple's MagSafe charger made wireless charging ridiculously easy for me. The magnets built into the charger and the back of the phone mean the two easily snap together and start the charging process.</p>
<p>You can charge at up to 15W on most iPhone 12, iPhone 13 or iPhone 14 models if you have a 20W charging plug at the other end, which fortunately I do. However, if you own an iPhone 12 mini or iPhone 13 mini, then that's limited to 12W. That's still faster than basic Qi wireless charging though, and it remains just as convenient no matter which model you own.</p>
<p>Although my AirPods don't have magnets in the back, I was still able to charge them fine with the MagSafe puck. It will be even easier if you own a newer pair of AirPods Pro though, which now comes with a MagSafe-ready charging case. If you're a diehard Apple fan, this is probably the wireless charger for you.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699507437837.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3pitaka-magez-slider-2">3.Pitaka MagEZ Slider 2</h1>
<p><strong>The best wireless charger for versatility</strong></p>
<p>It's fun just to play with the MagEZ Slider2, since the spinning mechanism that allows the stand to face any direction makes a satisfying clicking sound as it moves. But lock the stand in place and you've got a cleverly designed charging stand that's ideal for users wanting to power up their phone and several accessories in a limited amount of space.</p>
<p>The main iPhone charging section only powers your phone at 7.5W rather than the full 15W, but it's also a removable 4,000 mAh power bank in case you need a little extra juice on the move. The rear charging panel has a magnetically adjustable stand to help you charge your earbuds in the optimum position, plus there's another USB-C output for charging other devices. Keep in mind though that the &quot;Power Dongle&quot; accessory that you need to charge your Apple Watch is not sold with the standard version of the charger. If you need a space for your Apple wearable on the Slider2, make sure you buy the more expensive version that comes with it included.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best external hard drives]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-external-hard-drives/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-external-hard-drives/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-08T05:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The best external hard drives are essential devices for all PC users. That's because an external hard drive makes it easy to quickly and seamlessly transfer large files between your machines, especially if you have a slow local connection. This not only saves you time but potentially money as well. Whether you're working from home or at the office, carrying an external hard drive in your backpack or pocket gives you continuous access to your files.</p>
<p>The same is also true if you need to back up your computer regularly. A large HDD-based external hard drive will do the trick for that, but if you need to create a second backup for peace of mind and keep that in a separate location, an SSD-based drive will suit you. Thankfully, these aren't the slow, heavy external drives of the past.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699420991632.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1wd-black-p50">1.WD Black P50</h1>
<p><strong>A stylish, expensive external hard drive</strong></p>
<p>The WD Black P50 comes from respected hard drive manufacturer Western Digital. As such, it’s not surprising that it’s one of the best external hard driver you can buy. This SSD features 1 TB storage space, as well as a stylish, durable design and very quick transfer speeds.</p>
<p>Granted, the P50 is extremely expensive as these things go, offering similar storage to other SSDs at approximately twice the price. That’s arguably because WD designed the hardware with PCs in mind; indeed, you can get better performance if you hook the P50 up to a computer. But if you’ve got the money, it’s one of the best external hard drives you can buy.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B07YFGTDV4&asins=B07YFGTDV4&linkId=8ad779229aa219be01b1d08c916c9878&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699421239586.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2sandisk-extreme-pro-portable-ssd">2.SanDisk Extreme Pro Portable SSD</h1>
<p><strong>The best versatile hard drive</strong></p>
<p>No matter what you want from the best external hard drive, the SanDisk Extreme Pro Portable SSD delivers it.</p>
<p>Convenient design? It’s small and light enough to fit in your hand but not get lost in your pocket or bag. Suave looks? Its rounded corners, black-and-red coloration, delicately pockmarked front and soft-touch back give it an appearance and feel that are both thoroughly modern and refreshingly classic.</p>
<p>Ok, how about speed? The USB 3.1 version of the Extreme Pro Portable SSD is rated for sequential reads of 1,050MBps, and in our own performance tests, it routinely came out at or near the top of the rankings. The SanDisk Secure Access application applies general encryption, too.</p>
<p>The drive is a shade expensive, and the integrated carrying loop is too big to easily fit on a standard keychain. Otherwise, this is an excellent storage device that's ideal for heavy everyday use.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B08GV9M64L&asins=B08GV9M64L&linkId=9d2fc94758e57a346907822e42c5aa22&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699421363047.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3wd-my-passport-ssd">3.WD My Passport SSD</h1>
<p><strong>A speedy and colorful portable drive</strong></p>
<p>The WD My Passport SSD with USB 3.2 doesn’t look like its travel-enabling namesake, the My Passport Go, but it’s all ready to go places. It’s small (3.9x 2.2x 0.4 inches) and attractive, with its shiny ridged surface and choice of five snazzy colors (blue, gold, gray, red, and silver).</p>
<p>With a price per gigabyte of $0.19, the 1TB model is one of the most expensive drives we tested. And its included USB Type-C cable is exceedingly short: 6.5 inches, which makes using this drive a bit of a hassle on either laptop or desktop computers. (A Type-A adapter comes in the package to ensure the drive will work with a wide variety of systems.) But these are small nitpicks that don’t detract from one of the best external hard drives around.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B08F27QGHX&asins=B08F27QGHX&linkId=1aad29df576919875b7024593daf72ef&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="4"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699421498560.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="4samsung-portable-ssd-t7">4.Samsung Portable SSD T7</h1>
<p><strong>Sleek meets speedy with this portable SSD</strong></p>
<p>The Samsung Portable SSD T7 looks like the T5, with its rectangular figure adorned by rounded corners, though it’s a little bigger and heavier and its software is identical. It comes in somewhat more exciting color choices, with Indigo Blue, Titan Gray, and Metallic Red variations available for its 500GB, 1TB, and 2TB capacities.</p>
<p>The biggest difference is that Samsung rates the drive at 1,050 MBps, and we saw much higher results in our tests. It completed our file copy test 20 seconds faster, for example.</p>
<p>But with a cost of $0.23 per gigabyte, this is one of the most expensive drives we’ve seen (though you may be able to find it online for cheaper). If you care more about the Samsung name, the drive’s design, and the speed than you do about value, the T7 delivers more than enough to appreciate and justify itself.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B087DFLF9S&asins=B087DFLF9S&linkId=a3c6ca7040fa4d23e9cfc702f61e6566&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-monitors/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-monitors/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-07T06:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Whether you’re a professional video editor working from home or want to experience the best PC games at their finest, the best monitors can have a transformative effect for both work and play.</p>
<p>The best monitors you can currently buy will make every computing task you tackle in your daily routine that little bit more pleasurable and hassle-free.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699337078204.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1dell-se2719hr">1.Dell SE2719HR</h1>
<p><strong>The best monitor for general use</strong></p>
<p>For a monitor that's great for everyday use and won't cost an arm and a leg, the Dell SE2719HR is our pick. Sometimes you just need a reliable, inexpensive display, and based on user reviews, this is a great one to get. The 27-inch Dell boasts an IPS panel, so the display will look great from any angle. While it won't match the resolution of a 4K monitor, the display is still sharp and clear, with vibrant color and deep black levels. With only HDMI and VGA inputs, it's not ideal for gaming (DisplayPort is better suited to the higher frame rates of a GPU), but most any other use should be ably handled by the 27-inch display, thanks to its minimal lag times and 75Hz refresh rate.</p>
<p>An adjustable stand lets you set the angle to your comfort and liking, while the bezels around the display are surprisingly slim. And with a relatively small stand, the footprint of the monitor is compact enough that you won't have to give up much of your desk space. Heck, with the sleek design and affordable price, you just might pick up two for a dual-screen workspace. For our favorite monitor in terms of function and value, the Dell SE2719HR is the best monitor on our list.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B07KW6HFD1&asins=B07KW6HFD1&linkId=5368b66a4c5838923bbd0623cb39c485&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699337206005.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2apple-studio-display">2.Apple Studio Display</h1>
<p><strong>The best monitor for MacBook owners</strong></p>
<p>The 27-inch Studio Display ($1,599) is a great 5K monitor, one that delivers a lot of the value of Apple's $5,000 Pro Display XDR in a much more affordable (though hardly cheap) package.</p>
<p>Like the Pro Display XDR, the Studio Display offers useful features for creative professionals, including a range of reference modes and P3 wide color gamut support. But it also has unique features that any Mac user can enjoy, like a killer (for a monitor) six-speaker sound system and a 12MP ultrawide camera that supports Apple's Center Stage feature, courtesy of an onboard A13 Bionic chip.</p>
<p>With its ultrawide camera, fantastic speaker setup and gorgeous 27-inch 5K screen, this is easily one of the best monitors for MacBook Pro owners seeking an external display.</p>
 <p align="center">
 <iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B09V3GZD32&asins=B09V3GZD32&linkId=e0a1283fc000540c23e472f3e9ecd94e&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699337313484.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3samsung-odyssey-g9">3.Samsung Odyssey G9</h1>
<p><strong>The best when you absolutely, positively, need the biggest curved monitor possible</strong></p>
<p>Samsung's curved 49-inch Odyssey G9 Gaming Monitor is a strong overall performer, but its unwieldy design and sky-high price do not make it ideal for everyone.</p>
<p>Boasting top-notch functionality and impressive performance along every metric, the Odyssey G9 is worthy of serious consideration from anyone who can make full use of it. So if you have a high-end graphics card, a spare $1,700 or so, an excess of desk space (or a sizable hunk of wall), a stuffed-to-bursting game library you want to apply a unique (and not always completely complementary) visual spin to, and not much desire to use the monitor for everything else, you probably won’t be disappointed. Plus the next generation of the Odyssey G9 Neo, which replaced the original G9, is tipped to be the world's first 8K ultrawide curved monitor. Truly astonishing if it comes to fruition.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B096YNP6ZR&asins=B096YNP6ZR&linkId=d62c2833cd810078f04f00444128c014&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Wi-Fi 6 routers]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-wi-fi-6-routers/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-wi-fi-6-routers/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-06T07:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The best Wi-Fi 6 routers can give your home network a major upgrade, especially if you’re still using an older Wi-Fi router or one from your Internet Service Provider. Besides providing you with excellent speeds and a strong Wi-Fi signal, Wi-Fi 6 routers come in two varieties: Wi-Fi 6 routers and Wi-Fi 6E routers.</p>
<p>While a Wi-Fi 6 router will improve the performance and speed of your home network, a Wi-Fi 6E router gives you access to the new 6 GHz band along with the 2.5 and 5 GHz bands. Not only does this prevent network congestion as your most important devices can use this newer band, but the 6 GHz band is dramatically faster, albeit at a much shorter range. We’ve rounded up the best Wi-Fi 6 and Wi-Fi 6E routers for apartments as well as both small and large homes with all of the features you need to completely upgrade your home network.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699255126492.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1asus-gt-axe11000">1.Asus GT-AXE11000</h1>
<p><strong>The best Wi-Fi 6E router for gamres</strong></p>
<p>The Asus GT-AXE11000 is a Wi-Fi 6E gaming router that delivers excellent speeds, killer gaming features and awesome customization options. This tri-band gaming router also uses seven high-performance 160MHz data channels in the 6Hz band to help distribute a lot of data to nearby devices.</p>
<p>At the back of the GT-AXE11000 you'll find a 10G and a 2.5G WAN port, four gigabit LAN ports, a USB 3.2 Gen 1 x 1 port and a USB 2.0 port to connect all of your wired devices and even to transfer data from a hard drive across your home network. There's also Asus' built-in AiProtection security software to keep everyone and everything on your home network safe online.</p>
<p>In our testing, the GT-AXE11000 was able to reach a maximum speed of 2.96 Gbps at 15 feet with an overall range of 85 feet. It's dedicated gaming features are nothing to slouch at either. If you want a powerful gaming router that's futureproof thanks to its multi-gig ports, the GT-AXE11000 should be your first choice.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B08RWBPBBR&asins=B08RWBPBBR&linkId=258c318fa996f57f6efd4cbfc9a35317&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699255308260.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2netgear-nighthawk-raxe500">2.Netgear Nighthawk RAXE500</h1>
<p><strong>A Wi-Fi 6e speed demon</strong></p>
<p>The Netgear Nighthawk RAXE500 was the first Wi-Fi 6e router to hit the market, and the results are mind-blowing. By adding a 6-GHz band to the already impressive capabilities of Wi-Fi 6, the Nighthawk RAXE500 delivers category-leading performance.</p>
<p>With an AXE11000 rating, the tri-band device more than lives up to the hype by delivering nearly 2.5 Gbps of real-world data. Add this to the slick design and highly customizable configuration options, and the Netgear Nighthawk RAXE500 becomes one of the best routers we've ever reviewed, and possibly the fastest.</p>
<p>By adding access to a slew of new data-delivering channels in the 6-GHz spectrum, the tri-band Netgear Nighthawk RAXE500 takes the lead as the first high-performance Wi-Fi 6e router. While it’s best at close quarters and is quite expensive, the RAXE500 is worth every penny if you have the need for speed.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B08R58D9FH&asins=B08R58D9FH&linkId=41c1123fca0f7bb49886a249a591c23c&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699255408075.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3asus-rt-ax86u">3.Asus RT-AX86U</h1>
<p><strong>The best Wi-Fi 6 router overall</strong></p>
<p>The Asus RT-AX86U is a Wi-Fi 6 powerhouse that delivers great speeds and killer gaming features, as well as awesome customization options, all for under $300. With high-end performance and lifetime protection against intrusions and malware, it's also a great option for securing your entire home network, providing long term protection without a subscription fee, and carrying a two-year warranty.</p>
<p>But the real draw of the Asus RT-AX86U is the performance, which approaches the the magical 1-Gbps mark to provide speedy and effortless connectivity for all of your devices.</p>
<p>With excellent range and great performance — even through walls and between floors — the RT-AX86U is equal parts general-use router and elite gaming router, and the collection of features and ports it offers are a steal compared to some of the top-performing gaming gear. If you want the best Wi-Fi 6 router for the whole household, the Asus RT-AX86U is it.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0BQ417K47&asins=B0BQ417K47&linkId=3f24431ab74672e1fa7424a630c601d5&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best smart TVs for streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-smart-tvs-for-streaming/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-smart-tvs-for-streaming/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-04T02:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The best smart TVs for streaming are instant portals to the world of apps and can whisk you away to services like Netflix, HBO Max, Hulu and more.</p>
<p>Not only are the fast and easy to navigate, but the best smart TVs also offer robust search engines that can find the exact shows and movies you're for and they often come with features like Chromecast Built-in or Apple AirPlay that will allow you to send whatever you're watching from your phone to the TV.</p>
<p>Some of these features can be found on streaming devices like the Roku Premiere, Apple TV 4K or Amazon Fire TV Stick 4K, however, it's often more convenient for people to have those smart TV platforms built right in. That way, you can use one remote to jump from streaming services to live TV.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699063960246.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1sony-bravia-xr-a95k-oled">1.Sony Bravia XR A95K OLED</h1>
<p><strong>Amazing brightness and black levels plus the best smart TV platform</strong></p>
<p>By any standard, the Sony Bravia XR A95K OLED is a remarkable TV — and often, it’s far better than that. This set, which sits at the top of Sony’s expansive TV lineup, unites the industry’s defining technologies and Sony’s own groundbreaking processing and picture enhancements to deliver superlative performance in every area. And our own test results back this up.</p>
<p>What makes it so great for streaming? Google TV is in serious competition for the simplest, cleanest, and richest smart TV interface, and it’s right at home on A95K. Simple and quick to navigate, easy to search, and adept at presenting plenty of new and recent options without overwhelming, it makes finding and watching movies, TV shows, and anything else a breeze. And Google TV’s seamless integration with Google Assistant helps still more, letting you search for things as easily on the TV as you would your phone or computer.</p>
<p>The question with the A95K, then, isn’t whether it’s one of the best streaming TV you can buy. It’s whether it is the best TV you can buy. In our opinion? Yes, yes it is.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699064123366.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2samsung-qn90c-neo-qled-4k-tv">2.Samsung QN90C Neo QLED 4K TV</h1>
<p><strong>This premium Samsung QLED TV is big, bright and beautiful</strong></p>
<p>When looking for a 65-inch TV that offers great performance without a super-steep price tag, the Samsung QN90C Neo QLED TV is the QLED TV king thanks to best-in-class brightness and impressive performance across most content genres.</p>
<p>Powered by Samsung’s high octane Mini-LED panel, the QN90C promises excellent performance across the top genres. For those who aren’t familiar, Mini-LED backlighting delivers high levels of brightness while maintaining realistic color and gradations of luminance. And though the QN90C Neo QLED isn’t the most premium of all the 4K Samsung 2023 TVs, it’s the one that you’ll probably be most tempted to buy.</p>
<p>Its gorgeous 1-inch-thick design contains a huge array of smart features, potent Dolby Atmos sound and HDMI 2.1 connectivity for gamers that measured in at an impressive 9.8-millisecond lag time in our testing.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0BTTVL419&asins=B0BTTVL419&linkId=a76fa21060cafd4c4acc65dabef3f661&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699064230532.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3lg-c3-oled">3.LG C3 OLED</h1>
<p><strong>The most celebrated OLED TV series is great for gaming</strong></p>
<p>If the top-tier Sony is a little too expensive and the ultra-vivid Samsung hurts your eyes, the LG C3 OLED can be a perfect compromise for gamers.</p>
<p>What makes this the top gaming TV? Features like Variable Refresh Rate (VRR) and Auto Low Latency Mode (ALLM), which you’ll find on many newer TVs equipped with HDMI 2.1, as well as tweaks such as black and white stabilization, blue light reduction, Dark Room mode, and more. The C3 is rated as Nvidia G-Sync Compatible, and it supports AMD FreeSync Premium. You can even specify the genre of your game, and the C3 will apply settings designed to optimize its picture for it.</p>
<p>The LG OLED C3 easily lives up to its predecessors’ hype and presents a compelling case for itself as part of the newest generation of TVs. No matter what you want to watch, this set will make it sparkle and if you’re a gamer, you’ll benefit from its performance and dizzying selection of dedicated features.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0BVXJ69F4&asins=B0BVXJ69F4&linkId=2c8da25b8cc185c966a41de2db2fe19e&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best Samsung phones]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/best-samsung-phones/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/best-samsung-phones/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-03T05:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The best Samsung phones rankings reflect a busy year for the smartphone giant. Not only have we seen new Galaxy S flagships and improved foldables in the last 12 months, but Samsung has also come out with budget devices that should appeal to anyone looking to save on their next smartphone.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1698988343468.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1samsung-galaxy-s23-ultra">1.Samsung Galaxy S23 Ultra</h1>
<p><strong>The best Samsung phone you can buy</strong></p>
<p>As well as being the new top Galaxy S model, the Galaxy S23 Ultra is also one of the best phones around generally, beating even the usually indomitable iPhone on photography and performance in some areas.</p>
<p>The new 200MP camera proves to be very versatile, offering wonderful detail and color depending on your priority. The overclocked version of the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 chipset offers lots of power too, while the display is as colorful and bright as ever, even though Samsung's improved the phone's power efficiency.</p>
<p>Samsung's still asking for a lot of money for this phone, and has stuck with the divisive curved display, even if the angle's less extreme than in previous years. We're also unimpressed by its charging speed, which even at 45W is a bit slow.  But if you've got the cash to splash, you won't get a better Galaxy phone right now than this one.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0BLP2G96N&asins=B0BLP2G96N&linkId=1bbd0b06424798c41dc90b8c425d89a8&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1698988427294.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2samsung-galaxy-z-fold-5">2.Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5</h1>
<p><strong>The best foldable phone from Samsung</strong></p>
<p>Samsung didn't make dramatic changes for the Galaxy Z Fold 5. In fact, Galaxy Z Fold 4 owners will likely be able to skip this version of the foldable phone without regret. But if you're new to foldables, this is Samsung's most polished version yet, thanks to a new hinge design that makes the Fold both thinner and lighter than it's ever been.</p>
<p>The biggest addition to the Galaxy Z Fold 5 is the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 for Galaxy silicon. You get top performance from the chipset, which is the same one found in the Galaxy S23 series. But the bigger benefit is battery life. For the first time ever, a Galaxy Z Fold performs well on our battery test, holding out for more than 11 hours. That's not only better than the average smartphone, it's also an improvement over the Galaxy Z Fold 4's sub-10 hour time.</p>
<p>The newer silicon also helps with image processing, so the Galaxy Z Fold 5 turns out better photos than before even if the camera specs are unchanged from its predecessor. We wish Samsung would start adjusting the price on the Galaxy Fold, particularly with the Pixel Fold costing an identical $1,799, but Samsung's phone re-establishes itself as the best foldable phone overall.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0C63F7F2P&asins=B0C63F7F2P&linkId=68a02ef9c0416d7574e86df5c6ea8f33&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1698988550950.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3samsung-galaxy-z-flip-5">3.Samsung Galaxy Z Flip 5</h1>
<p>The Samsung foldable for most people</p>
<p>Like the Galaxy Z Fold 5, the Galaxy Z Flip 5 doesn't see big changes from its predecessor. The same Flex Hinge found in Samsung's other foldable is on display here, too, and the new design helps the Flip to fully snap shut at last. But the bigger change comes to the Flip's outer display — instead of a 1.9-inch strip, you now get a 3.4-inch panel that's big enough to run more widgets without ever having to open up the flip phone. Unfortunately, there's a limitation — you can only run select apps on the Galaxy Z Flip 5's outer display. (That's not something Motorola Razr+ owners need worry about.) Still, we're happy to see the Flex Window arrive on the Galaxy Z Flip 5.</p>
<p>We're also happy with the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 chipset powering the phone. You get better performance, sure, but you also get improved battery life over past Flips — the Z Flip 5 now comes close to the average battery life for smartphones on our test, which is a big improvement over the Z Flip 4. Unfortunately, other phones still outlast Samsung's flip phone.</p>
<p>At $999, the Galaxy Z Flip 5 remains Samsung's most affordable foldable phone. It's good news then, that Samsung continues to offer a solid phone at that price, though we'd like to see more substantial changes down the road.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0C63F8MWR&asins=B0C63F8MWR&linkId=a1fc522b3e713f09e9a38cfd2f34f985&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best noise-cancelling headphones]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-noise-cancelling-headphones/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-noise-cancelling-headphones/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-02T05:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The best noise-cancelling headphones are a must-have for all forms of public transport, as anyone who's worn a pair on a flight or a train commute to and from work will tell you. ANC headphones have gone from strength-to-strength over the past couple of years, with many models improving their audio performances compared to predecessors.</p>
<p>The pick of models below represent the greatest ANC over-ear headphones across we've seen (and heard). Over-ear headphones often have superior noise-canceling performance as the earcups form a seal around the ears.</p>
<p>Read on to discover what are the best noise-cancelling headphones you can buy right now.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1698903145527.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1bose-quietcomfort-ultra">1.Bose QuietComfort Ultra</h1>
<p><strong>Best-ever over-ear headphones for noise-canceling</strong></p>
<p>The Bose QuietComfort Ultra Headphones are the best ANC headphones overall. As the replacement for the Bose 700, the company has raised the bar yet again for active noise-canceling headphones, effectively silencing outside world around you. The new model throws in Immersive Audio tech and plenty of extras including Bluetooth 5.3 with multipoint connectivity, aptX Adaptive support, and touch volume control. This all comes in an all-new modern and lightweight design that's comfortable enough to be worn for hours.</p>
<p>There are multiple levels of noise cancelation to balance the level of quiet with Aware mode (transparency) to suite your surroundings. Battery life has been extended to give up to 24 hours, while changes made to the controls and design make usability more practical and seamless.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0CCZ1HQ39&asins=B0CCZ1HQ39&linkId=280c05da8b8237b96dfca56785974011&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1698904060554.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2sony-wh-1000xm5">2.Sony WH-1000XM5</h1>
<p><strong>Best balance of elite sound and noise-canceling performance</strong></p>
<p>Sony has been steadily closing the noise-cancelling gap on Bose, and the new Sony WH-1000XM5 comes closer than ever to beating the Bose 700 in terms of its ANC performance. It has two processors controlling eight microphones, where the 1000XM4 (still on sale and regularly discounted) before it had just one processor controlling four, and the result in our testing is near-seamless ANC.</p>
<p>During our testing we found that sound quality is superb, the 30-hour battery life (with ANC) is excellent and everything from the touch controls to the ability to tweak the EQ via the Sony Headphones Connect app is well thought out and seamlessly integrated. Call quality has also been improved greatly and there's really nothing to criticize here beyond the slightly bland styling and the $50 price increase over the XM4.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B09XSDMT4F&asins=B09XSDMT4F&linkId=5f84dea346215aa61ff299859a5a7df4&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1698904088706.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3apple-airpods-max">3.Apple AirPods Max</h1>
<p><strong>The best noise-cancelling headphones for iOS</strong></p>
<p>Although there’s only one level of active noise cancellation on the ultra-premium AirPods Max, it works like a charm. The cans do a great job of blocking out ambient sounds, especially at the lower end of the frequency spectrum. It’s almost as good as Bose’s ANC, which is a fine showing for Apple’s first pair of over-ears.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, the AirPods Max sound great, especially with the surround-sound spatial audio feature switched on, and their design standards and build quality are so high you can almost forget that these headphones cost $549. That’s a lot more than the Sony and Bose headphones higher up the list, so this is a luxury purpose, but can very much be a worthwhile one.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B08PZD76NP&asins=B08PZD76NP&linkId=f98f9b50ea7c2213a761a9ee469c8887&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best tablets]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-tablets/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-tablets/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-11-01T07:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The best tablet for your needs can be tricky to find, whether you're looking to outfit the kids with cheap, durable tablets for school or just want a beautiful second screen to keep near the couch.</p>
<p>We can help you find the right tablet because we review the best from all the major manufacturers.  Based on my team's years of hands-on testing and reviews, we recommend these slates as the best tablets on the market right now.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699254567618.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1apple-ipad-pro-2021">1.Apple iPad Pro 2021</h1>
<p><strong>The best tablet for power users</strong></p>
<p>Apple's super-powerful M1 chip is the driving force behind the iPad Pro 2021. That chip set new tablet records in Geekbench and Adobe Premiere Rush — continuing Apple's tradition of putting tons of brawn in its sleek tablets. And this 12.9-inch model benefits from Apple's Liquid Retina XDR display, which offers much higher brightness — up to 1588 nits! Also, Apple includes a video conferencing trick called Center Stage, where the camera tracks and follows you as you move during calls.</p>
<p>Oh, and the basics are still stellar. Its quad-speaker setup booms, its optional Magic Keyboard offers a comfortable typing experience — and its battery life is better than last year's (lasting hours longer than the Galaxy Tab S7 Plus). That said, the super-bright XDR display needs HDR content to thrive, and that's not always available — as the likes of Hulu and HBO Max have yet to adopt it. Also, the 12.9-inch iPad Pro 2021 is more expensive than the MacBook Air (and heavier when docked with its Magic Keyboard). But, still, the iPad Pro 2021 is worth it for creative pros who want the best tablet for their next masterpiece.</p>
<p>In October 2022, Apple released the iPad Pro 2022, which upgrades the processor to the more powerful M2 chip. It's a great tablet with solid performance, but only a nominal upgrade over the 2021 version.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0932FPL4F&asins=B0932FPL4F&linkId=83ac7882cbc3ca8ff21b443136da1609&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699254746462.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2samsung-galaxy-tab-s9-ultra">2.Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra</h1>
<p><strong>The best Android tablet when you absolutely need the biggest screen possible</strong></p>
<p>The Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra ($1,199 to start) is the ultimate Samsung tablet for those who absolutely need a ginormous slate.</p>
<p>Like its predecessor, the Samsung Galaxy Tab S8 Ultra, this year’s model features a gorgeous 14.6-inch OLED display, an ultra-slim svelte design and plenty of power thanks to its speedy Snapdragon 8 processor. If you’re ingrained in the Samsung ecosystem and need a tablet with laptop-like functionality, the Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra should serve you well.</p>
<p>Of course, Samsung’s monstrous tablet isn’t flawless. While you can use it as a laptop when it’s paired with the Samsung Book Cover Keyboard, the accessory adds an extra $349 cost to an already pricey $1,200 machine. And while the Tab S9 Ultra is a light 1.6 pounds, its large size can make it cumbersome to use when compared to a smaller tablet.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0CGDMCK77&asins=B0CGDMCK77&linkId=2b24bcfe22bfbc63c0ab016ef42c4767&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699254825069.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3apple-ipad-air-2022">3.Apple iPad Air 2022</h1>
<p><strong>The best tablet for everyone</strong></p>
<p>As great as the iPad Air 4 had been, the iPad Air 5 that replaced it hits a sweet spot between portability and power. The iPad Air 2022 is ideal for consuming and creating content, and its $599 starting price is within reach for many people.</p>
<p>Thanks to the addition of M1, the iPad Air 2022 is almost on par with the iPad Pro. That isn't to say the Air is now a Pro replacement, but the gap in power is considerably smaller. This, along with the iPad Air's relatively affordable starting price, could make this model more compelling than the iPad Pro for budget-minded shoppers who still want the best iPad their money can buy.</p>
<p>Overall, the latest iPad Air is an almost perfect tablet. While there's still some room for improvement, it's hard to put this sleek, powerful slate down. This is arguably the best tablet for most people, and one of the best iPads to boot.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B09V3H386P&asins=B09V3H386P&linkId=5f02a3ac5badcedcbd19996184d92283&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best noise-cancelling earbuds]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-noise-cancelling-earbuds/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-noise-cancelling-earbuds/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-10-31T05:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With the best noise-cancelling earbuds you can block out the sound of the world around you. They're discreet to wear while having unbelievably powerful active noise cancelation technology that makes distracting external sounds fade into the background.</p>
<p>Read on to discover which of these top-performing noise-canceling earbuds have the right credentials for your needs.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699336077788.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1bose-quietcomfort-ultra-earbuds">1.Bose QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds</h1>
<p><strong>Best ANC performance from a pair of wireless earbuds</strong></p>
<p>The Bose QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds have gone straight to the top of our buying guide for their outstanding noise canceling capabilities. They replace the still available Bose QuietComfort Earbuds 2 that launched in September 2022, and perform even better. These are a remarkable follow-up that brings the same top-tier noise-canceling performance while introducing immersive audio. With better stabilizing fin alignment, they deliver improved fit and stability and the Bose QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds could be ones you wear all day long.</p>
<p>The Bose QC Ultra Earbuds include aptX Adaptive support, making them compatible with high-performance audio codecs increasingly supported by the best Android phones. If you're after the best-in-class ANC from a pair of wireless earbuds, these are the best I've tried.</p>
 <p align="center">
  <iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0CKBJ7SC4&asins=B0CKBJ7SC4&linkId=bbaffcb73e2aae50a2e87b7789f51d64&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699336315375.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2sony-wf-1000xm5">2.Sony WF-1000XM5</h1>
<p><strong>Best Bose ANC alternative with top-tier features</strong></p>
<p>Sony's XM-series earbuds go from strength to strength with each new generation. As the latest flagship, the WF-1000XM5 wireless earbuds are smaller and lighter, yet they're equipped with some of the strongest features and performance I've ever seen from a pair of wireless earbuds. In my review, I found they had some of the most dynamic and engaging sound I've heard, and their noise-canceling performance easily matched that of the Bose QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds or Apple AirPods Pro 2.</p>
<p>Battery life hasn't been stepped up over the outgoing XM4 predecessor. But at 8 hours with ANC enabled, these top-tier Sony wireless earbuds still outperform close rivals and have some of the highest battery life of any set of more recently launched earbuds. There's LDAC support for higher-quality music streams form compatible devices, adaptive listening mode, Google and Alexa digital assistant support, and full EQ customization.</p>
<p>Call quality is greatly improved, thanks to a new noise reduction engine with AI that's able to make voices clear even in noisy surroundings. Wind noise was kept to a minimum too, thanks to the mesh on the feed forward microphone helping to reduce its influence during calls. Ultimately, I found these to be Sony's best-ever and one of the most versatile wireless earbuds you can buy right now.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0CBKS4THP&asins=B0CBKS4THP&linkId=faf1839c8df454f765705040cbc01fe7&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699336425600.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3apple-airpods-pro-2">3.Apple AirPods Pro 2</h1>
<p><strong>Strong ANC performance and adaptive audio</strong></p>
<p>Apple's AirPods Pro 2 bring significant upgrades to the popular AirPods Pro original.  Along with the USB-C version and a new suite of adaptive audio features, the AirPods Pro 2 are Apple's best-ever ANC earbuds. I regularly use them on my routine work commutes and at the gym.</p>
<p>Externally, they look pretty similar to the first generation but battery life has been increased to offer 6 hours on a single charge from the earbuds and a further 30 hours from the wireless charging case. The Lightning version of the Pro 2 earbuds are IPX4-rated, while the USB-C version has been upgraded to IP54 for both the earbuds and the wireless charging case.</p>
<p>Designed for iPhone owners looking for a more tailored listening experience, these are the pinnacle of Apple technology and the USB-C version may sound even better. On the audio front, Apple has included a new H2 chip with custom amp and driver that delivers better lower and higher frequencies, and you can use the iPhone's TrueDepth camera to create a personalized spatial audio sound to listen to some of the best Dolby Atmos sound in any pair of earbuds. Noise cancelation is double what the original AirPods Pro offered, and gets remarkably close to the pool of silence conjured up by the #1 Bose QC Ultra Earbuds.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B0BDHWDR12&asins=B0BDHWDR12&linkId=f3bb64d206fd26e7edf42d0b79f1d8de&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-mouse/</id>
        <link href="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post/the-best-mouse/">
        </link>
        <updated>2023-10-30T05:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Picking up the best mouse can make every task you approach easier. With a good pointer beneath your fingertips, you should be able to glide around the screens of the monitors with ease.</p>
<p>When choosing the best mouse for you, it’s important to consider price vs. performance. If you can spare the cash, it’s worth investing in a mouse with high DPI (dots per inch); a factor that directly affects how quickly your cursor moves across the screen.</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="1"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699419948495.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="1logitech-mx-master-3">1.Logitech MX Master 3</h1>
<p><strong>The best mouse overall</strong></p>
<p>The Logitech MX Master 3 is the best mouse, at least on the productivity front, as well as the best wireless mouse. It's comfortable, feature-rich and lasts an amazingly long time on a single charge. This sleek gray peripheral is part of Logitech's MX Master series, and everything the company has learned from the previous iterations is on full display. The buttons give satisfying clicks, the grip is pleasant to hold and the horizontal thumb wheel makes scrolling through documents a breeze.</p>
<p>The software is where the MX Master 3 shines, however, as it comes preinstalled with a variety of different functionalities for popular programs. From Photoshop to Excel, Logitech has already predicted how you might want to use the horizontal scroll wheel and gesture controls, and developed optimized profiles for each program. You can also use the handy Logitech Flow feature, which lets you drag and drop files between two totally different computers, as though they were connected via USB.</p>
<p>The MX Master 3S improves on its predecessor, but the MX Master 3 is still one of the best mice you can buy.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B07XC2FWD1&asins=B07XC2FWD1&linkId=1a9064bc05c2b450daeae857663d996f&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="2"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699420054296.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="2logitech-mx-vertical">2.Logitech MX Vertical</h1>
<p><strong>The best ergonomic productivity mouse</strong></p>
<p>The Logitech MX Vertical flips the idea of an ergonomic mouse on its head — well, more accurately, on its side. This mouse is essentially what would happen if you squished a productivity mouse, then made it stand upright. It's a little hard to describe, but once you see the MX Vertical in action, you'll know right away whether it's for you. If regular mice strain your wrists through small, repetitive motions, the MX Vertical might offer some relief. This is because it forces you to move your whole hand around, thus minimizing the strain on any one muscle.</p>
<p>Aside from that, the mouse is classic upscale Logitech goodness, from its adjustable DPI, to its durable build quality, to its robust software that lets you drag and drop files across two computers with Logitech Flow. It might just be the best wireless mouse for workers who struggle with wrist strain.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B07FNJB8TT&asins=B07FNJB8TT&linkId=cddc8ca9347c779ab58ad232cfef72ed&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>
<figure data-type="image" tabindex="3"><img src="https://bestchoice.long-trip.com/post-images/1699420137955.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></figure>
<h1 id="3razer-viper-v2-pro">3.Razer Viper V2 Pro</h1>
<p><strong>The best esports mouse</strong></p>
<p>The $150 Razer Viper V2 Pro is billed as a wireless esports mouse, but it’s also ideal for everyday use. This is due to the device’s lightweight, nondescript design, and its exceptional battery life. A slew of customization options via the Razer Synapse desktop app also lets you tailor the mouse's functionality to your tastes.</p>
<p>As the successor to the Razer Viper Ultimate, the Viper Pro 2 has a lot to live up to. But Razer fans can rest assured that the Viper Pro 2 lives up to its predecessor, and earns its premium over cheaper mice, such as the Razer Orochi.</p>
<p align="center">
<iframe sandbox="allow-popups allow-scripts allow-modals allow-forms allow-same-origin" style="width:120px;height:240px;" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&OneJS=1&Operation=GetAdHtml&MarketPlace=US&source=ss&ref=as_ss_li_til&ad_type=product_link&tracking_id=bestchoic0695-20&language=en_US&marketplace=amazon&region=US&placement=B09VCSKB1C&asins=B09VCSKB1C&linkId=43b1d4c6c7304be84ac1fd8c00037086&show_border=true&link_opens_in_new_window=true"></iframe>
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>